You poor little fella.
ര്രടി്ത്ധ.
It's all right.
1ഒണലുല്വാമ.
Big Mama's here.
ദ്ര ഗീണാ ഠി ഠി ട്വ.
You know, you're gonna need some caring for.
ദ്ധ ലിസ, ത്വാഖ 03.
Now... Now, let's see, darlin’.
ഗി... [ഗി 09 ബം ടത.
You need...
ദ്ധാലിധ...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
൨ ലപലപലിപ്ല്പലം.
Not me. Not Big Mama, now.
ധി മിവ. ദധിന്ഥ രാണ, ്ധ1ട്സ.
Now I'm thinkin’, though.
ശബ മവ ടലി ലീന.
Now... Now don't... Don't you move, honey.
പനാ... [ഈ൭൩... പനാ ത്ധാജുല്ല്ം ടമാ.
Big Mama's gonna be right back.
ദ്ര ഗണ കന ദ്ധ!
Good work, Boomer. We'll get him this time.
ദാറുധട, 8ഠഠണല്‌. ദ്ര ൩ ന റ്ല്വാദ ഠി.
I think he's in there.
൧൮ മട ഠ1ദ മഠ ഠ। 519൬.
Am I glad I found you boys.
ധാധ്പാില്ഡയാണസ്ധിത്ഖ.
There's no time to lose. I need your help. Now come on.
0309 സയ നടമ. എവവാലിധാലസ്ധ ത്വ. വീടി.
- Come on. - Let's go, Boomer. Come on.
-്‌ഗീലിലവ. - കയവിറ, 8ംഗനല.[ഗിട1ല.
Yeah, but... Oh, shucks.
൭, ട്വ... ൨൩ കടി.
Oh, poor little guy.
൭൩൭5൨0 ഠ[9.
Don't you worry now. We're going to find someone to look after you.
പദാ ടട്യഷ്ധ്ണാ. ദ്രണി ലോ ഹ്മാ ധന്ധിലത്ഖ.
Hey, I think I got an idea.
റല, മിവട വ ഠി ഠാ.
OK, Boomer, now you know what to do.
൭൦ ദംഗനല[, ടല്യഷ്ാ ദ്വ ലസ ല്വാ നല്ഗധ്ധ്‌.
Yeah, leave it to me. Leave it to me.
൭, ടല്യ്വിത്ഥ ഠ്വ. ലദ്വിക്വാദഠ്ല്വ.
Who is it?
ടല?
Well, l was sure l heard someone knocking.
൨, മവ മടി ഠി യാ നന്യബ്ബിടി.
Oh, dear! My laundry!
൭൨, ശ്വ യ്ബാല്ധ ലിഡ്‌
Oh, here! Stop it!
വപഘ! ദന!
Oh, you pesky birds! Will you come back here?
ഠപത്ധവാധസ്നു ലര! 8ഠില്നത്ധ ക്ട ാദ॥ന
Oh, stop!
പാലിന്‌!
Well, 1 wonder what got into those birds.
൨, ല്വാദില്വ്ഭന്മ ധസനാ-ാഥസ്ണായ.
Well, bless my soul!
൮൨, ൨, ന൫5ടടി01യ്‌
Why, it's...
൧, ല്‍...
It's a baby fox.
൧ഗിസ്പടണ് സ്ഥ.
Hello, little fella.
ലിം, ടര ൫0.
l wonder where its mother is.
(൫ നന്മ ണടിസമ മുലസ൭.
Come on, now. I'm not going to harm you.
1-111-11 എവ ലിഠിത്വ ടോള്‍ ത്വ.
Now, now. Oh, isn't that...?
൧൨, ൦൨. റ്പാധിത്ബ്ഖ്വ്ധ...?
Oh, my, my. You're a feisty little rascal, aren't you?
൨, ടി. !ദ്ധാല്റാദ്ധി, ദത?
There, there, now. Calm down.
810, 0൧൭0൭. 8 ബല്ല.
No, I just can't leave you out here all alone.
1-1 0-111-11. നാലി ത്നത്ധ ടല ടബ്‌.
Oh, isn't he darling?
൨, സിഡ യഖ്ന?
Now, not so fast.
ഒം॥റിഖ൩നാ൩ ലോഖ്‌ ടാ.
Now, now, not so fast.
81916൩99, 10൦0 ലോ ടാ.
Oh, my. You're such a little toddler.
൭൨, ഡല ദ്വ ബഈരുട 0ബി.
Say, that's what I'm going to call you.
ലല, ധി ഠി. ധില ന്മ ത്വ.
Tod.
100.
You know, Tod,
ദ്ധ ട്വ, 7900,
I'm not going to be so lonesome anymore.
1181111111!
I got a surprise for you, Chief, old boy.
ചവ മഠ ടദ്ധാാട ധ്ന്ധിലിത്ധ, വല്‌, 'യഥബിവ.
Now, now, now, take it easy.
810൭൩, ൧൮09൩, ലലല.
Well, how's this for a huntin' dog?
പ്ും൩,ാട്റമ്നടന്മ ബി ടലാദ്റ! ബ്ബ സ്ഥ?
He's just a little runt now, but he'll grow.
൧19 ൫൦ ൭൮! ടലഖ്ണു, ദ്വ ഠി മിയബാടട.
You may as well get used to him, Chief.
ദചപിധത്ധിടലിയ്വ റി ഠബാ്സഭ, ഠ്വില്‌.
He's for you to look after from now on.
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ [൮3 ഠി ഠ്ലി ടല.
Tod, stop pestering Abigail.
10, 0൦൩ റു ഷാ.
Abigail, you're going to have to be patient with Tod.
൧, മ്ധ നടട്॥ി ലട ഠാ ഠഠി.
He's one of the family now.
ലയ്വനാ ഠി ണ്ട ഭ്്ഖ്യ ൯൭.
Oh, of course. Now I know.
൭൨, സ്വസ൭. ചവ ല്ഡ.
I declare, I never will get my chores done.
ബില ഠിം, ലിറമ്നന്മ്വ്ടഭഷ്ധവ.
Oh, mercy!
൭൨,൦1൩
Tod! Tod, stop it!
100! 700, ലാഠണല്സി!
Abigail! Abigail!
ല്ല! ചില!
Oh, no! There goes my milk! Oh, no!
ധപ്ാബ്‌ ലാട ട്വട്ധ ലിവ്‌ ഠപ്ാഒ്ബ്‌
Easy, easy, Abigail.
ദല, 0, ഷാ1931.
Steady, old girl. Steady.
ദല, ടി ഖ്ന്മ്വ. 8 ലല.
There, there.
വ്വ റിമ, ധ ഠിഒ.
Tod, you come here.
100, ദ്ധ നി ൫ ട്വ.
Il said come here!
ചയത ന്ഥ ട്ല്‍്‌!
Just look what you've done.
ന്റ ലായ ത്വ 010൮5.
Now, don't try to butter me up.
ലയ്വബാവന്ബത്ധ നഠിവാലന്നട്ബ]ദ ഠ്ണദ്ബ്വ.
Oh, Tod, I just can't stay angry with you.
൭൨, 7൦0, ടിഡി നല്്വിത്ധ.
You little imp. Now run along and play.
ദ്ധ ടി ൭൦ നവര. ലലറ്ില്വാണ്നല്ല.
And try to stay out of mischief.
ഉബ്യാബബാധദ്ലാടട.
Hey, it's Dinky and Boomer. Maybe they wanna play.
ലല, ൮ ഥല്‍ 0 8൦ഠണല്‌.. ദം നര ന്ധധാപ്ണട്ന.
Is this it, Boomer?
വിവ ഠി, 8ഠഠനല?
Sure, Dinky. This is the place.
൭, ൧൦. ബില്വന്ധ്സു.
I never forget a tree.
൧൮ മിലാണ്ല്വ്ധാട 001൭.
He won't get away this time.
ദ്ര ൩ ഠി ഗ്ലാ.
Hold it, Boomer. I think I hear somethin’.
ലസി, 8ഠഠനല. എവ മട മഠ ബു ടടട്ധദ്ധ.
That's him, all right, Dinky. That's him, all right.
ധില ഠിം, ധി ദ, ല്‍. ല്വ ഠി.
Get ready, Boomer.
8ലടടഠിഒ, 8ഠഠനല.
Hey, I can hear him movin’. Listen.
റല, മവ ന്യ ിവാുല്ല ഥല്‌.
That's funny. I don't hear nothin’.
ലല॥൦ ൧൮ 131 ല്ാദ-ല്ലാമ.
Quiet.
൧1൬.
That's him, Dinky. That's him, all right.
ധില ഠിം, ൧(ബിവ. ഴി, ധിലി ഠിദ.
Button your beak, will ya?
ധ്ധ്വ സ്ധഥനഥാ ത്വ, ല്ല
I'll check it out.
൧ിവവാല്യ]ി ലാലി.
Would you look at that?
8ഠില്നത്ധ നാം?
OK, Boomer, he's right... there.
൭൦ ദംഗനല, ഠിവാദ്ധി... [൮ ഠ19.
Yikes! Watch it!
ലല! പൂമ!
Why, you...
(രന്്വാമ, നവ...
Nail him, Boomer! Sock it to him!
ല്ിഥിട, 8ംഗനല്‌! ദലിത്ബവാദഠ്ബുമ!
Hiya, fellas.
ലി, യ്ധാലഠ്വഒ.
What ya doin’? Wanna play?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാാധ പപടി്വാന്നദ്ന?
Stay outta this, kid. This don't concern you.
പനാ ്വാധ 150൦൦. നി ബധിര ന്ലിത്വ.
Let him have it!
ദലിത്ബവാദഠ്ബുമ!
Don't let the creep get away! You can take him, Boomer!
പദ്നാബ്ബല്ലിത്ഥ ദി! !ദ്ധാഠിലല്‍ ഘാ(യ്വാ ഠി, 8ഠഠണല്‌!
Give him a left! A right! Let him have it!
വിവി ടലാലദ്വനന! ദന്ബ ദലിത്ബവാദഠ്ബുമ!
- Which way did he go? - This way.
- (൫ നട്ട ഠി്ാലയ്്്‌? - (൫ ടമ്മ.
There he is!
ഠി!
What happened to ya? Golly!
൧൧൭90 0൭0൭ ദ്ധ ഗവ്‌
Oh, shucks! I think I bent my beak.
൭൨, ട്വ! ഗ്രന വ ൧1൪൦.
Now see what you done? You cost us our breakfast.
ന്യ ല്വായ്ധ ഠ്മ്വാധണ? ദരി മില്മ ടാഘ്വാണിതണി.
I cost us our breakfast? It was your fault.
1-111-11: ബ ടലില്വിത്ഖ.
- What are you talkin’, my fault? - Yeah, yeah.
-൧്യാടന്ധ യ്മ, ടി ലിവ? ര.
A worm? For breakfast?
ഒലല്യ ധി ന്ധി ട്്വാണ്‌?
Hey, there, Copper, what ya sniffin' at?
റല, ഠല്ല്രാല്‌, ദ്യ ഖ്വ നന്യ്വ?
Somethin’... l never smelled...
൭ടട്ധദ്ധ... ൮ ലവ 3ാണട10 ദ്ധ...
... before, Chief.
...ടലാല്ധന [ബ, റ്വില്‌.
Let me see.
[ഗി ലിവ ൭0൦1൦
Shucks, that's easy.
൧൮ ടണ്ട്ാ.
The master's just cookin’ grits and fatback. You oughta know that.
പ ഡാബിന്ട നനടടല്റുമാഥാ ബി ണലപദ്ധ നടടി ട്വ.
That's not what I smell.
ദധിത്ന്ധുത്നാ മഡാാദ്ധ.
I don't know, Chief.
ച്വ ലഗ്്ഡ, റിവീല്‌.
It's something else.
ബി ഥണ്യ്ഃ 1൭0.
Sonny, you got a lot of learnin' to do about a-sniffin' and a-smellin’.
ബഖി ത്ധലാണ്൨ ട്സ ന1വല്മനാ നന്യ്വഠെ ഠ്ക്ബാദ്ധ.
Hey, where you goin’?
0൦, യ്വ ലിധഭ നദ്ന്മ?
I want to find out what that smell is.
എവ ന്മിഥലി ദ്ാദ്ഘ്വാദ്ധ ്.
OK, Copper, but the master ain't gonna like you wanderin'’ off.
൭ ലാല, ടല ഡദ്ബിദ്മ 13100 ധി ര്ധ നട്ജുര്ധ.
I won't get lost, Chief. Il can smell my way back.
ച്‌ (ലഠ൭്൨ ടടടം, റിവില്‌. ൧യാഠില്‍ നലന്യ്വഠ്ധുട്
Can't tell these young whippersnappers anything.
൧ഗി്മഗന്ധഠ്ദല്‍്‌ 191 ഠിബുല്‌ യമ.
What ya smellin'?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധ നല്യ്വ്വഠ?
I'm on the trail of somethin’.
ചവ നല്യി॥ധ്ധ്ല്ല ടടട്ധബ്വ.
Trail of what?
പില്ലിഗ്വാദ?
I don't know yet.
1111:
Why, it's... it's you!
ഠ൦൩ത്വ... ഡ്ധാസല്‍!
What do you do that for?
(രന്ല്വാദ്ധാധബ്ാട്്ധ?
We're supposed to do that when we find what we've been trackin'.
ഴിണഘാ ഡമി ാധമ 019 ഠ്ല്വാദ ല്ലാ ഠ്വ.
I'm a fox.
൧൮ ടലലയ സ്വടഉ.
My name's Tod. What's your name, kid?
പ്ൂംനലിവ ഠഠ. ൧൧൭ നന ര്ധ,വാധഠ്ട്റ
Mine's Copper. I'm a hound dog.
പ്ൂംനമലിവ ഠ൦ഠലലല്‌. ൧൮ ബന് ഗസ്ബാധ്സ.
Gee, I bet you'd be good playin’ hide-and-seek.
പലി, ട്ഡടാടസ്ധിത്ധ 00 ാല്നട്ന നബ.
Wanna try it, Copper?
ദ്ധ ന്മഗഥ്ഥാം, ഠല്ലലാല?
Can l use my nose?
8ഠില ലിവ റ്റ ബഠ്ധയ്വ?
Sure. OK.
1ന്ധസ൭. ൭൦
Now go ahead and close your eyes and count.
ലയ ഡ്്വാനമ്ട വ ഠി 010.
One, two, three...
ടദ്ഖ, ഠ്വ, 193...
No, Copper! You can't peek!
111 റല്ല്രാല! ദ്ധ മിഗംിപ്ബന്ലി!
Now start again.
ടലിയ്വബാവാധമ്‌ ടണ്ഡിദ.
One, two, three, four,
ദല, ഠ്വ, 9, സ്വാ,
five, six, seven...
നദ, എന്മനം, ധി...
My, my. Look at that.
77൭, ഡല. നേം.
A fox and a hound, playin’ together.
ശ്രടഘാ ൦൦ ബ്ന സ്പാധ്സ, ല്നല്ലാല്ടണടമ.
When you're the best of friends
219 4൭൧ ലക ൧൭൧0
Having so much fun together
2്ലടഥ്രാല്ടഥേക ലട
You're not even aware you're such a funny pair
കഥ ഒട ാഥ (രഥ ലോറ ഒററ ററ
You're the best of friends
കഥഥല്ക്ഥെ 7ട്യാദ ലര്‌
Life's a happy game
൧ഠ്ഥ൧ ൧൨ ൧ലനദ്ഥടെ 77൭
You could clown around forever
൭൧ ൧൧ല ഥല്റഥഥ ലന
Neither one of you sees your natural boundaries
79൭ ഖാ ക്ഥറ്റ ഗദ ഒ്രാദ ൧9൭5 ലഗ്‌ ഗ്ഒ
Life's one happy game
൧ഠ്ഥ൧ ൧൨ ൧ലനദ്ഥടെ 77൭
Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌!
Gee, I've gotta go.
ല്‍, മവ നട്ട രായി.
If only the world wouldn't get in the way
കരദഥ്ഒ വ്ഗ്വ൭ ഒനണറ്ഗടറെന്നഭ
If only people would just let you play
ക്രരഥ സന ഗാറെട്ത്ഥ (രഥഥാലന്നഥെ ടഒഒ
They say you're both being fools
ഗദ്ലലഷ (൭ഒ :൭൧ 2ഠറാഠഗ7 ഥലഡ്ഥ
You're breaking aif the rules
ലററ ലട
They can't understand
്ലടഭ൭ (ഒറ്റ
The magic of your wonderland
(രഥ റ്ഥഒ (൭൧
When you're the best of friends
219 4൭൧ ഥല്‌ 7ട്യാ
Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌!
Sharing aif that you discover
28ലഈററ൭ ഓട) ഷ൧ഥറ്റ (രഥ റ്്ഠാ൭%
When these moments have passed Will that friendship last?
219 779൪ ൧ല്‌ഒ7 ൭ര൭൪ഗ ലലലാ ഥ്‌
Who can say?
കദാ ഷ്ഥറ്റ ഗഗ
There's a way
൧ീറ്ദ ഒറ
Oh, I hope
൨൧, ഒ
! hope it never ends
൧ ഒ ഒഥലടഗ
Come on, Copper!
ഗി, ലാല്‌
‘Cause you're the best of friends
ട്ലാദ൧ (൭ഥ ഥല്‌ ഗ്വാ
Copper, you're my very best friend.
ഠല്റ്രാല്‌, ധ്വനി ഖ്ധബ്വനു ജവ ടട്യി.
And you're mine too, Tod.
ദ്ധാഥ ലാ ധന്ധിിവ, 1൦9.
And we'll always be friends forever, won't we?
ഉന്മ ലിത്ഥാലിത്മമന ടല്ദണാ-1ണസയ, ഒന
Yeah, forever.
൭, ടല.
Hey, let's go swimmin'!
റല, നി ൯9ാലയി ലാല!
Give me a head start and I can beat ya!
ദ്ധ്വാല്യ]ി ഠ്ധ്വ ൭൦൩ 1൮ മിത്ബിവയ്ല്വത്ിത്ധ!
Dagnabit! That Copper pup's gone and strayed off again.
ട൩൭! ഗലി ലോല വാല്യു! നടയയരദ്ധ ദ.
Come on, Chief.
മീലി, ബില്‌.
If that little rascal's gonna make me a good huntin' dog,
ദ്രിദ്ധ ടി നരി ഭി നിലുദഠി സ്ബാധ്ഡത്റാ ടിം
he's gotta learn to mind.
ഠി നട്ട്‌ ഠ്ലാല യ.
Copper! Get over here!
ഠല്ലാല്‌ '[ഴീലി ഭ ടബ്‌!
Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌!
I gotta go home.
൧൮ നട്ട്‌ ധി.
Do ya have to? We're havin' too much fun.
ദ്ധ നടിയ? ഗ്മ ടലോമന്യു ാല്ട്ധിര 0.
I gotta. He sounds awful mad.
൧൮ നടടി. ൧1 ലാധസസമ നല്ഖ്വാട്ി.
I'll see ya tomorrow!
ചഡ്ൃധന്വാ ന്ധ ടട
- And don't forget! - L won't!
-൧ബൃണ്യ്ബിഥ്ാ! -൧ിവ ടില്ധാട!
Hey, Copper, what happened to ya?
ല്‍, ഠല്ല്രാല്‌, 3190 ാ3ഠിട ന്ധ?
Why didn't you...?
(രന്ല്വാ ദ്ധ ലി൦..?
Golly! You're all tied up.
ദ്ധ ഠി॥ര.
Yeah, and it's no fun either.
൮൭, 990 8ദല0001റാഖ്ബി.
The master says I gotta stay home.
1-111-11 1-1 ട്വ നട 9! ഠി ബണ്.
Well, we can play around here then.
ദ്വിധാ, ന്മ 0ഠില ാല്നമഥ ഠി ടി.
Oh, no. Not with old Chief over there.
൭൨, 0൦16. ടവം ബല്യ ഠിം ഠി ട്ട.
Is that him making that awful noise?
ഗിലിയ്സന വി ൮ ഠം൦ബ്ബ?
He keeps me awake at night.
എവ ലിറ്റ്‌ ധഡല്ഡ നിണ.
Oh, don't go in there! He can get awful mean!
ധപ്ണാണ നടടധില്ഭ ട്ട! പ്ുംസ ദ ന്ലിഗ്മ്്വ്‌
He's cranky.
൧19 റു.
Gee-whillikers, is he ever big.
എചിനല്പാടടസ്ുദ ഒ.
His ears isn't as big as yours, Copper.
ലനാ 1൭1: ടലോടടല 1ല്ബാട ത്വ, ഠല്ല്ാല.
That's not the part you gotta worry about.
ധിത്ല്ധത്ാത്ധ ഗല്ധ സസാ.
Wow! Look at those teeth.
77൭൨ ഹും9ല് ലിസ.
That's the part you gotta worry about!
ധിലി ൮ ത്ധലാല്ധ സ്റ!
I'm gainin' on him.
൧൮ ല്‌ ന്മ ലാ ഠി.
- He won't get away now. - He's wakin' up!
- ൧ 110്ച്ാ്ിച 3. - ൧ ൭1 ന്ധി ടല!
Get out, Tod!
ല്ധല, 7ഠഠ!
No. He's havin' a dream. He's chasin' somethin’.
1 (ദ ഥന്ബ്ന്പാ!. ൧19 നലല ടടട്ധബ്വ.
When I get him cornered...
8॥ വ ശ്വാന 913...
It's... It's... It's a big old badger.
ബ... ല്‍... ബീ ടടലരയ ന്സാല്.
Copper, he's chasin' a badger.
ഠല്ലരാല, ഠി നല്ല്ല ടയ ന്പാലന്യ.
No, no, it ain't a badger.
1ലിപ്ലില്ബ്‌ധാധിക്ന നസ്പാല്ണ.
Iisa... Itsaf...
ബി ടടലയ... ബ സ്വ...
It's a fox. A fox?
ബി ടടല്യ സ്ധപടാ. 'ശ്രടബ?
Run, Tod! Run!
1, 100! 1!
Tod!
10!
Amos Slade, you trigger-happy lunatic!
൧നഠട 3120൦, ധ്ധ നലലസ്പാനമഠണ 91-91!
Give me that gun!
ഒലി ടവ ട്ഘ്വാബാഡ!
My radiator!
ടം: 1-1
Why, you blasted female.
(രന്്വാമ, !യ്വ ലഘ്വ്ധമ്ന 1൭.
- Hold it right there!
- ൧൮... മിവ... - 8 ഠ। ട്വ ടല!
Watch it! That thing's loaded!
൨0-൫൩! ലല്വാാ വ ്ാല്ഥ്ധ്‌
Now it ain't loaded!
ടലയ്വാ ല്ല!
Dagnabit, woman! Your thievin' fox was after my chickens!
കബ, ാലഭന്വാധബ്‌ 'മ്വടണാ നല ത്വ നഹാല്ല മണ മയ്‌
Rubbish and poppycock!
ദ്വ ന്‌
I don't believe it. He wouldn't hurt a thing.
ചവ മില്മ വ. ൧19 1510൭0 ലേഠില്ദ ടടടില്ാമ.
You callin’ me a liar, you muddleheaded female?
!ദ്ധിത്ട ടവ ൦0, ധ്ധലാല്ന്പാധബിഭ്ിബ?
- l saw it happen! - Amos Slade, that temper of yours
-൧ിവ 0൫5 ടണ്ഡട്ധ! - ൧നഠട ടദഠല, ൮൮3 ടഒ നല്്വിത്ഖ
is going to get you into a lot of trouble.
19 മിയബാദ്ഖയ്ധ 1.
Temper?
ദ നല്ഖ്ന?
Temper, woman? You ain't seen my temper!
9 നല, ഹലഘന്ഥ്ധന? !ദ്ധാല്ധണ അര!
If lever catch that fox on my property again, Ill blast him!
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലിവ॥നമസ്ധടണ്ധ ഠി ഠാ മയി, ടവ ലിത്ഥ ്ബാല്റ
And next time, I won't miss!
1-111-11“: 1-1
Poor little tyke.
(രട്സുദഒ ടി ഭി ഡ.
It's a shame I have to keep him cooped up.
ദയറാ മവ നാം ഡാ ഠി ഠി ഠ്ല്മണ.
Tod, stop looking at me like that.
10, 500൭൦൩ ൭0൦1ല്വാാഘ്റ്ധ.
It's not my fault, you know.
11:11: 11:11
You caused a lot of trouble yesterday.
ധൃത ധമ ബഖി്ധിയാദ്ധ ടണട!ഒണ.
Oh, now what are they up to?
൭൨, ടല ട്വ3 ൮ നല്ട്യ്വാധമ?
Why, it looks like Amos is going on a hunting trip.
൧, നന്വാലിസുദ ൧൩൦൭ ന൭1ലാലയ! നസ്പാധ്സ.
A long one, from the looks of it.
പും സ്ഥലിസ൭ ഠി മഖ്ബ്വായ! ണ൮0953.
Well, good riddance!
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാവ, ലാഖ്യിട്നത്ധ!
Doggone meddlin' female,
൭ ലല്വ്ധമന ഹാന്റഠ്വേ,
shootin’ up my radiator!
1്ബാലമഠിഒ ഭഘ്ട വ!
Dad blame it. Get goin'!
൧൮ ടടില്വത്ഗ ഠി. 8ല്ല്്ബ്ല്വ്‌
There. Well, that's more like it. Keep runnin’, old girl.
പം. സില ലിവ നട്ധ. ലിന ബട, ബ്വ്ബ്വ.
Well, Copper, me and old Chief are gonna teach you all about huntin’.
ഠല്ലാല, ടവ ടി ഡാ ബല്‌ ടിക ല്ലത്ധ നാഥ.
Yes, sir. It's about time too.
ധി. ൧ ട്വാട! നടാ ാഥ.
Attaboy.
ദാറ്ധടസുഒ.
Yeah, you're gonna like trackin' down those varmints for me.
൭, ഴ്വ ലിക്ഥ ടിയ നല്്ധ്ല്ല്റന്മ്നു ഡധനസ്ധിറ്വ.
Get in the back, half-pint.
ഉധഠ്ധിറ। ാല്ല്യ്വാ, ടി ൭൦].
You gotta earn your right to sit up front.
ദ്ധാലധ്നദുര ്ധഠ്ധിി ഠ്ല്ാദ ഠാ.
Well, boys, we're gettin’ outta here till next spring.
8ം॥9ിട൩യ്ധ ടപസ്ധട, ന 0 ന്ന്യാദ സ്വടിന്പാഥാമ.
Tod, honey, what are you doin' over here?
10, ടത, ദ്യാമന്ധ വ ടബ്‌
Gee, I just wanted to say goodbye to Copper,
എവ ഡന് നമോ ടലദണമ്‌ 10003 !ഭ്വാദഠിദ ഠവ്ര്ലാല,
but I'm too late.
ദ്വി ടവ ലില്ധ വമ്പ്‌.
Well, what did you plan to do if you ran into old Chief?
1ല്॥, ല്വായ്ധ ന്ലവാധമ ിയാലന്വ ണോ ഠവല?
Chief. I can outfox that dumb old dog anytime.
ബല്‌. ഷവലാഠില്വാലഠ്കുഖ്ക്ന ഠി 0139-01 നട.
Tod, now hold it just one minute.
10, ്റാഠ്ധ ടലാന്ട്വ.
Didn't you learn anything yesterday?
ദ്ധ മഗധലില്യ്ല വാലാ ടണടിടണന്‌?
Now you listen good, Tod,
ദ്ധ ഠ്ബുല്‌ ലിലാദി ഠാ,
because it's either education or elimination.
ടലാദ്ധ ബല്‍ ഹന്യല്മ്ഡമ്ണ ദ്ധ ാലന്യന്ല്വാധടമ.
Now if you're so foxy and old Chief's so dumb,
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ടണ്‌ 05 ൦ വില്‌ ാല്റ്ധ ാഠഠ൦1,
then why does that hound get the fox on the run?
199 ല്വാ്ഖ ബു 0ഠ1ല 0൮൭ സ്പടബമി?
‘Cause he's got the hunter, and the hunter's got the gun.
ലാലാ ഠി ഠിഹാ്ബാസ്സാഥസ, ബ്ലാ സ്ബാഥ്ബ മഠ ടപ്ഘ്വാല.
Elimination. Lack of education.
ലല്റ്ഘ്വാധടന. പ്ര ഥ്യഖ്മ്സമണ.
If you pal around with that Copper hound
കഥ കഥ ഥല്ക്ഥറെ റ്റെറുറെ 5! ൭൮൩൮ ൧0ല൩൧൧൧ 0ഠല്ഥാല 7
You'll wind up hangin’ on the wall
കഥ ഒഗബ്ൃഭ ലുറഗറ്റ ന്‌ വ്റവ്ഥറ്റ
Keep your nose to the wind You'll keep your skin
കഥ നട്ട ഥാക്‌ ഥു (൭൧ ൭ ലര്ഥ നഴ
‘Cause you won't be home when the hunter comes to calf
ക്ലാദ൧ (൭൧ ഒ ത്ഥ ഒറ്ദ 2൧ഒ9 5 0ല൩൧ ൧൭
Oh, Big Mama, I know Copper would never track me down.
൨, ല്ലാ ഗണ, ലവ ട്സ ഠല്ല്ാല 151 ॥വ്ധുല്ല1ഠവ.
Why, old Copper, he's my best friend.
ലാലാ, ടി ഠല്ല്ാല ഠി യന ഭ്വാമ്‌ വ.
Your best friend.
ദ്ധ ഭ്വാദ്ിത്ധ.
Now, Copper's gonna do what he's been told.
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌ മിയാ! ദ്യാത്റാ ഠി ഠിടധബി.
Supposed to chase the little old fox into the old foxhole,
ദ്വ നഘാല്ല സ്വടണ നടട്ധിലിഭ ധാന,
then along comes the hunter with a buckshot load.
ഭന്ധഠിക് മ്മ ടി ാസമ്പാധസ ബു ടണ്ഘ്വാാ ല്ല.
Elimination.
ലല്റ്ഘ്വാധടന.
Lack of education.
പ്ര ഥ്യഖ്മ്സമണ.
You better believe it, Tod.
ചിധത്ധവാല്മയ, 100.
Yes, sirree!
൭, ധി ഠ്ല്‍
You mean Copper is gonna be my enemy?
[ഗീഭ്ധഠ ദ്വ ലാല്‌ ടിയു! സ്വട്ധി ലയ?
Hey!
പ]!
Kid, you better step over here and take a good look.
ചിധത്ധ ക്ട ഭ ട്ബ്‌ ൭൩ 0൦10ധലിലാദിം നിം
Why... Why, that's awful.
(രന്ല്വാ... ല്വാ, ൨ ലര ടല.
Those poor things.
(൫ടട0 നല്‌.
I'm sorry, Tod.
[ഴീദല്‌, 700.
Honey, Copper's gonna come back a trained huntin' dog.
ദയാ, ല്ലോല്‌ ലഖ്ബാധിാ ടലാദ്റ! ബ്ബ സ്പധസ ലിറ.
A real killer.
൭ലലയ ്പാധന്ധി.
Oh, no, not my friend Copper.
൭൨, ൯ഠലിപാധിത്നിയ്മ്ബിവ ഠ്ല്ാല.
He won't ever change.
൧19 151 മിബാലധാല.
l hope you're right, Tod.
൧വഘഘ്വാ।ന്ധ ബി, 100.
And we'll keep on being friends forever.
ഉ ഖ്മ്്‌ ല്ഖ്ബദഠി യല ടലണട-1നബുഒ.
Won't we, Big Mama?
ധിനയ്ബിയി ലവ, ദ്ദ?
Darlin’, forever is a long, long time,
ന്ന്‌ ടല്ദണമ-1ണട ധി നട,
and time has a way of changin’ things.
൭൦൩ ണനടടവാഠിലല്‍ നലാാധാട[ ടടട്ധദ്ധ.
Oh, Jiminy. It sure turned cold.
൨, ലിയ ടലി.
- I'm freezin' my b... - Hey!
-൧ിവ ലവ ഠി ഠ്൭5ന... - ല്‍!
It's that fuzzy worm! Let's get him!
ധിലധിബാധ്ധ യ! ഗ്ടാത്വാ ഠി!
Charge!
ഗി!
Hey, Dinky! Dinky, quick! Over here!
ല്‍, ൧൩൮ ൧൨, ലോ ൧ ടല!
I got him! I got him!
൧൮ ഠിലി ഠ്ച്യാമ! ഷവ 51 ലാണ്‌
Do I look like a worm? That's who we're after.
൧൮ ഠി ഡ്വാദ ധി ധില്സന ന്മ ലി.
Come on!
ഴ്വ
Look at that little creep,
ല്ല ട ഭയ ഖ,
warm and cozy by the fire.
൧നടടെ 0 ഥാട്ടല്്റാ ഠി ഠ്ലാദ്ന ലാ.
Let me take a look.
രല ടവ ൦.
Now how do you like that guy?
ദ്ധ ടധിര ഠിദഖ്ന?
Snug as a bug,
൭ലിടടദ ടല്ാലന്‍ ഖന്റാാമട,
while we're out here freezin' our beaks off.
ടല്മ്ാിത്ബിന്മ ഠി ട്ല്‍ ട്ഥാലി 0ലവ സ്ഥല ന.
Yackin' and shiverin' ain't gettin’ us anywhere.
8ലധിയ്വാ റ നാലല്ല ദ്വ മലര ന്ന.
We'll get that no-good worm when we come back.
ഗ്ല റാത്വാടി ഖിയ 019൯൭ ദാവാ
Oh, shucks.
൨, ടിസ.
So long, Big Mama.
ലണമ്‌ന്ന്യാല്‍, ദാന.
Yeah, we're goin’ south for the winter.
൭, ഖ്യ്്‌ ഭ ടട ടല്നടടാ സ്ധടിന ടല്ധിം
Goodbye, boys. See ya next spring.
ലന ന്നാല്‍ ദ്രവ. പ്ധന്വാദ 191 സ്വടിനസ്വാധ.
Well, look who's here.
1൦0, ടില്ലാമ ഠി ടി.
Oh, my goodness.
൨, ടി.
I'm sorry, Tod, honey.
[ഗാലി വ, 1ഠഠ, ടയ.
- [hope... - Hiya, Big Mama.
-൧ിവ ന്ല്ജ്വാ... - 19, 8 [ഗീടന3.
We're back. We flew all the way.
ദ്വി വാഡി. ദരി ണന ട്വ ൫ ടമ.
Yeah, we did. We did.
൭, ാട്ധി. ധ്വാഖ്ധി.
Welcome home, boys!
ലന ധി ഭ്വാദഠ്ദ ത്വ!
It's been kind of lonesome around here without you little rascals.
ധാധ് ണോ ടബ്‌ വ്യാ ടി നരി നണയ്വ.
Hi, fellas!
൧, യഗപ്യ്മല്‍്‌
Hey, who's that? Who's that?
ലല, ടിയാ വ? ടല?
This can't be that scrawny little squirt
ചിറമ്ബ്മ്വ്ധ ടി ൭൦॥
we found by the fence post, can it? Come on.
൮ ന ലയ മാല? 77൭൧൭൨.
I can't believe my eyes.
എവ മലാല ലാ ലിവ്‌.
Oh, it's me, all right.
്പ്ലില ല്ധ,ാഖി!.
Hey, looky there. He's got himself a real fancy collar.
0൭, 12 ഠി 5൫൭. ൧19 99 ഖല ലല സിം
Hey, hey, hey. Just look at this bushy tail.
൧൦, 06, ല്‍. ലിന്മില ല്ലാ അബ്ബാ ല്‍.
Beautiful.
ണിം
Come on. Cut it out. You guys are always teasin' me.
പ്നാബ0. 11. ദ്ധ ടലല്ധ ഗലി! 1൮.
Hey, it's him, it's him. Squeeks.
ലല, ധി ഠി, 1ധില ഠിദ. ടഠ്ധ൦ല്‍൭.
We'll see ya later, kid.
പ്ധന്വാദ രവ ഭസ്ധാ।ദ, നി
We gotta take care of some unfinished business.
ദ്ര നട്ട്‌ ദ്ിടിക്ന ട്ബ ഭു.
I can't understand.
എവ ല്വ്ല്നണന.
It was so healthy.
ഉല്ല ലട.
There. That oughta perk it up.
പൂം. ൮ ഠി ടലി ടന്ധിമ.
Now, where'd he go? Where'd he go?
(൫ നന്മ ഠദ ഠ്ദ്വ്യാലയ്്്‌? (൫ നന്മ ഠദ ലയി?
He's goin' up the drainpipe! I'll head him off.
൧1 നന്ദ ടി ല്ല ൧വിഷ്ല ഠി.
OK, Boomer, we got him trapped! Let him have it!
൭ ഒംംണല്‌, 09 51 ഭ്വാഥാ ഠി! ദലിത്ബവാദഠ്ബുമ!
- Did you get him? - No, I didn't.
- ദ്രവ ഠ്യ ഠി? - 1൦ മിവ 110്്വാട്‌.
Neither did I.
എിവ്ാഥ10്ച്രാ്‌.
Come on! Look!
ഴി നം
A caterpillar under glass. Oh, boy!
൭ലലയ ധിദ്ധാധ്ധ ഠാ. ഗ്്വ്‌
- Holy! - Smoke!
- ഗ്ന - ധി നല്ല്‌
Hey, hey, how's he do that, Dinky? How's he do that?
ല്‍, ാാല്നട്മ ദവ, ലിവ ദാറുല്നാന്മ ഠി ാധദ്റ്‌
ain't got no job I'ma huntin' man
4൧ ൭ ൭റ9 ക്൮ഒ ൧൧ ഠഥറ്റ നലന്ഥഥ
And I'd rather have a dog than a dollar
ഥു ഖധ ടഥ്ര ഒ റ്ദഗ്ഥ3റ9 ടഒ്ഡ റ്ാഠ൭൦
So let's go banjo ring-a-ling-a-ding-ho
പ്ദഗ്‌ ഒ൭൨(൭0 ൧ഒഥുഠ 00-9-7റ-9-റ്ററ-7ഠ
Give a little hoot and a holler
൧ഥ്ുനത്ഥ ടല! റ ഥേ
Come on, Chief.
മീലി, റിവ.
Just 'cause you're not sittin’ up front, that ain't no reason to be a sorehead.
ഠി ടലാലാ ദ്വ ദിഗ്ധഠ്ധിഠി ലാന, ഒബി ത്വ നല.
Shucks, if it weren't for you,
1-111-11 1-1 പന
Copper'd never have turned into a good huntin' dog.
ഠല്ലാല 151: യബ)ഠ। ട൦ട്യ ഒന ഗസ്പാഥ്ഡുത്നാ ടിം
Yes, sirree.
൭, ന്ധ.
Now I got me the best two dogs there is.
ടലയ്വാ വ ലാമ റബ ബ്ബ ണിം
Right, Copper?
ധി ലവ, ലാലാല?
Isn't he somethin’, Chief?
൧1 ാടറ്റട ൦, വല്‌?
Look, Big Mama! Copper's back!
ഹ്യ ദ്ര ഗ്ണ്ട! ഠല്ല്ാല 11 0൭19
Boy, has he grown big.
7൭, ്ദ്വാടടട്ല രാധ ഠി.
And look at that big pile of skins he helped track down.
ലിന്മില്വാല്ല്വാദ ബഖി ഡ്്നു ഠദ സ്വ നാലി.
I know, Big Mama. He's a huntin' dog now.
എവ ല്ഡ, ദ ഗ്ണട. ൧19 ഠടവ3ഠി മന്യ ഗനസ്പാധ്സ.
You're right. And you're a fox.
ദ്ധി. ൧ബിത്ധ സ്പടണ.
That won't make any difference. Copper's gonna be glad to see me.
ലിലി 05൭1. ഠല്ലാല ല്ധ റന്വനധന്വാദ ദവ.
Well, honey, just don't get your hopes too high.
റല, ടത, ദ്വ 1ബ്ു0 ന്മജ്വാിത്ഥ ടബ്‌.
Look, don't worry. I'll be careful.
പദാ. എയാണ്‌.
I'll go tonight when Chief and the hunter are asleep.
൧വവാല്യ]ി നമി ബ്‌ ॥ദ ബല്‌ ്ബ്ാസ്സാഥ്ബ ദ്വി.
Boy, it's great to be back home, isn't it, Chief?
ലഠ൦1വാബ്ധി ധി ഭ ബന, ധാധിത്ബാഘ്്ഡ, ബല്‌?
Come on, Chief. You aren't still sore, are ya?
പദാ, ഠവല. ലിറമ്ബ്മ്സത്ധ നദ്വി, വത?
Hey, hey, come on. Let's scuffle.
൧൦, ലി, നി. [ഗി ൧0 ഈഇഠന൦1-9ഠ൦നം1.
We ain't scuffled in a long time.
ഉ൫1ണ3 109 13ധാു൦ണം!.
Come on, Chief! Let's have some fun!
മീലി, റ്വ്ല്‌! ഗി 1൭ ൧!
Oh, lay off, Copper, you overgrown pup, you.
൭൨, യി, ലാല, വ ലഗ്ന ദത ടട.
Oh, let go!
ഠപലാടട്ത്ല്‍്‌
Dagnabit! Let go, I say!
എനറ ലാട, ടവ!
Oh, OK, OK.
൭൨, ൭ ൭൭
That was your trouble on the hunt.
ധില നടടില്വിത്ധ ടണടട നമ്പാഥ്സ.
Come on, old-timer.
മീലി, ഖ്വ ടി ൮2.
You treat me like a pup, you know that?
ദ്ധാധമ ട്വ നേ വന ഭി, ദ്ധ ല്ഡ?
Why, I think I done real good trackin' down them varmints for ya.
ലാ, മവ മട മഡാാദറ്വട ടല നല്വുല്ലാന്മ്നാ ധസ്ധിലത്വ.
Smellin' and trackin' ain't enough.
ഴി ൦൦ നല്ല്ല ട്വ 1൭10ഥ്വിഡ്വ.
You gotta think nasty.
ദ്ധ നട്ടി ലീ।നന൩ റുമ്നടട.
OK, OK, I know.
൭൦ 0 ദധാല്ഡ.
I know.
എവ ലസ.
Copper.
ഠല്ല്രാല്‌.
Hey, Copper.
റല, ഠല്ല്രാല്‌.
It's me, Tod.
ബ്‌ ലവ, 100.
I thought that was you, Tod. l heard ya comin’.
൧൮ ഠ്ല ടബ1ിയഡ ത്വ, 100. എവ ഠോ ത്വ ൭0.
Boy, you've really grown.
൨, ഴ്വ ദ്ല്വാടടല്‌.
You have too, Copper.
ധാ ലവ, ഠഠ്ാഥാല്‌.
Il saw you comin' back with Chief and the hunter.
എവ നന്വാദ്ലത്ധ ധി ലാന ഠവല ്ബ്വാനസ്പാധസ.
It's great to see ya, Tod.
ദാറ്വടധന്വാദ യവ, 100.
But, you know, you... You shouldn't be over here.
10, യവ ഡം, ത്വ... ദ്ധ ലി ടലാദ്ധബുദ ഠ। ടബ്‌.
You're gonna get us both into a lot of trouble.
ദ്ധ ടിയബാദ്മ നടി ധന്ധിലന്മവാല്്ധമ.
Hey, look, I... I just wanted to see ya.
റല, (ബും മവ... എവ ഡന്ന ന്ലിറ്ധന്ധാദ ത്വ.
We're... We're still friends, aren't we?
109... 11-11-11:
Tod, those days are over.
100, നടട ൨ റ ണ്‌.
I'm a huntin' dog now.
ലയ്വാ വ ബ്ന ഗസാഥ്സ.
You'd better get outta here before old Chief wakes up.
ചിധ്ത്ധ വായ! ലോ ടലാല്ഥ്ന ബ്ല ഥന.
Chief. He doesn't worry me.
ബല്‌. ചവ ടിലറട ഠി.
Tod, I'm serious. You're...
10, മിവ ിദ്വാലാദ്ധി. യവ...
You're fair game as far as he's concerned.
ദ്ധ ല്‌ നണട 0 ലാഠ്ബാമ്സു.
It's that fox again!
വ സ്ധവടണാഡിാ!!
Oh, no! No!
ധപ്ാബ്‌ പബ്‌
They're after Tod!
[ഴില്ല്യ നല്ല്ല 1ഠഠ!
After him, boys! Go get him!
ഷ്യ ഠി! ലല! 0ാിത്വാ ഠി!
Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌!
Copper! Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല! ഠഠലാഥാല!
Tod, I...
100, ലിവ...
I don't wanna see you get killed.
എവ ലിഗ്മ്ഡ॥മിത്ധ ഖ്ാഥ്ഡ്‌ന.
Track him down, boy!
(ഭടബല്്സമ!
I'll let you go this one time.
ചഡാാലിത്ിത്ധവാല്യി ൭ ബല്‍.
Don't lose him!
പ്ാബ്ബ്ലിത്ഥ ദ വി!
There they are! Old Chief's got him on the run!
നി ബല്‌ ധാധമ ഠി!
Jump, Chief! Jump!
[ഗ്വാ ബില്‌! ം്വാട്‌!
Chief!
ബല്‌!
Chief?
ബല്‌?
Oh, no!
ഠപ്ാഒ്ബ്‌
No!
പാബ്‌
Tod, if it's the last thing I do, I'll...
10, യിദ്ധബില്വാല്മ്ട ല്റ്ഘാടക് ലിവ, ടവ...
I'll get you for this!
പ്ട്റടില്വത്ധ നമസ്‌!
Tod!
10!
Tod? Tod!
1ഠഠി? 100!
Oh, Tod!
പി!
Thank heaven you're safe.
ല്യവിഡയിട്നത്ധ ടന.
Oh, poor Chief.
പടി റ്ീവില്‌.
And it's all my fault.
ഉ ടലി ട്വ.
I shouldn't have let Tod go.
എവ ടലാദ്ധസട 1ടിലാവലിത്ഠഠി ഖ്യ!.
Big Mama! Wake up! Wake up!
ദ്ര ഗീണാ! 8ദാഥ് ദ്യ
There's trouble!
൧൧൭ നടടടില്വ്‌
Tod! Well, what is it?
10! ചാട ഠി?
What on earth?
൧൧ ലിവ?
Widow, get out here!
ഉച, ഭ്ധലഭ ടലി!
Why, Amos! What are you...?
൭൨, ൧ണ൦ട ബ്വാസയ! ൧൧ ത്വ...?
Where is he? Where is he?
൧ നന്മ ഠി ൧ നന്മ ഠി?
I know he's in there.
എവ ല്ഡ ഠി ഠി ഠി ൭5൩.
Now just a minute.
പ്ും൩, ഡന്യാധ ഠ്വ.
You can't come bargin onto my property, Amos Slade!
ദ്ധ മില ദ്യ നല്ണ്പാധി 1൫ ഠ്ല്ല്ന ഡനദ്വവ, ഷ൧നഠട ടിദഠില്‍
That fox of yours almost killed Chief,
ശ്രടഘാ।യ്ധവ സ്ധിട നല്പാഥന്ധി ഠവല,
and I'm gonna get him!
൭൦൭ 1൮ ന്ലിഥ്ല്വാബിക്ഥ ഠി!
You can't keep him locked up forever!
ദ്ധ മാലി ഡാ ഠി ടലി ണു!
We met, it seems
ഗ്‌ ധാല്ലനഥ, 75൭
Such a short time ago
7ഒ(ലനട റ്ഥ്ഥ
You looked at me
കഥ നല! ഒ
Needing me so
ദ്ധ ഒധഥാഥ൭
Yet from your sadness
ഒ റ്‌ (കട ധ്നൈഥനഥ
Our happiness grew
ഗ(്രാടറദറ ശ്൫ നഗ
And I found out I needed you too
൧ുഒ്ണ ഖഗ റ്ട്രാദ7 ൭ഒധവാഥ ൧ഖ്൧ ൭ഥ
! remember how we used to play
൧ ഥറുലശ്ക ഥല്നദ്ഥ
! recall those rainy days
൧൧ ൧൭ ഗഗഗ ഗധ്റെ
The fire's glow
ഒഗഒ൭ ഒ നക
That kept us warm
കഥ നലനദറടടക്റ 'ഗ്൭
And now I find
ഥു (ഗ്ന ഖഗ റ്മ്വാദ?
We're both alone
ഗ്‌ ധാലയ്ഥ ഭഗ്വദ്റെ
Goodbye may seem forever
ക്ല ററ ഒക ലോലന്‍ ലേ ട-(ഒനഒ്ഥ)ട
Farewell is like the end
ടല റ്റ്‌ നഒ൦ഒന(ഒ0 ൧ലറ്ഗട്ഗ
But in my heart's the memory
7ഒഠ വ്റടഗധ ഒഠ്9 (കററ്ററെ
And there... you'll always be
ഥു വ്‌ ലല... (൭൧ ടട
Goodbye may seem forever
ടല റ്റ്‌ 7ഒടഒറ൭ “ലാല്‌ ലന ഒന
Farewell is like the end
ലോലന്‍ ലാറെറ്ഗ്ഥ!ട
But in my heart's the memory
7ഖ്ഖ്യ7 റ്റ ഒറ്ട (ക്ഥമ്ഥറ്റദ്റ
And there you'll always be
ഥു വ്‌ ടല (൭൧ ടലഒടെ
Hold it, sonny! Back off!
ലിലി, നിറ ദ്ധ്വാഖ്യി!
Consanrn it! Where...? Where do you think you're goin'?
ശ്യാഖ്ബുമ! 2൧ നന്...? ദ്ധ നാദത്വ ന്ല്ലഭ നട്ട്‌?
Oh, excuse me, I... I was just trying to...
൭൨, നടലിത്ഥ ലവ, ലിവ... എവ ഡന് ഡോ 03൦...
You barge in on somebody's house like you own it.
ദ്ധ ന്വാധ നടട്ധിബനണട പാ നാണ ബണ്ട്വിത്ഖ.
Tarryhootin' around them woods,
8ലിധിറ ഘാല്‌ ഠി ഡി,
wakin' up folks in the middle of the night.
നല്വുമാല്ത്ന വ്വ നടിണ്പാധ്.
l honestly didn't know anybody lived here, and I...
൧ഡാദ്ധി ട്വ ഠം ഹാ 1004 ഠ। ട്ബി, റ മിവ...
Well, you know it now. Now get off my property!
ഒറി, ടലന്വബാ ത്വ ന്ധ. ടലയ്വാ സദ ഠ്ം0 നനലിയ്‌
Go on! Beat it!
ലല്ല ദംമ്ബ്ധട!
I've been watching you, sir. You can stay with me if you want to.
വാലി ന്ധ 19൦, ഡ൩. ന1ന്യാലില ണോഖബ്ഡയാത്ദ്ധിത്ധന്ല്ഡ.
- That's very nice of you. - Come with me.
- ഥ്ാധ്പാലിലത്വ. ഗീ ഠ്വ.
She dropped that fox off at the game preserve.
൧19 നാലില സ്പടണാമ്ധ ഠി ണ്മ ൮.
We'll get him. We'll get him.
[ഗ്മ ലിത്൨ ഠ്ല്ാമ ഒ.
Well, now, if you gotta have a busted leg,
്9ഠി।, ദ്ധ ദ്വ ൫൭ നുര 0൭9,
this is the way to do it.
ധില ഖ്സയ.
Good food, soft pillow,
ഗിനാബാദാ്ധട, ൧൩3 സ്പാധ്‌,
warm stove.
ട്ല്യാധ ൮൭0൭ 090൭5.
Sure beats sleepin’ in that barrel.
1ലാവാലിറ്ങ്റാ്മ ഠ്ധ ടന 1൦0൭.
Well, now, here comes visitors to see the invalid.
ബി ഠദ ഹല ഠ്ദ്ബാ ധന്ധിനലല്‍02 ഒ ടിന്‌.
How do you like that? They didn't even ask how I'm feelin’.
ാൃുല്നാന്മ ഒടന്ധ? ഴില്ല്യ മിവ ലാധന ടവ ാല്ന്മന്മ.
Chief, get back in there before I break your other leg.
വല്‌, നടടലിറാ!॥:ടലാല്ന ദവ ഗദ്മ്വിക്ന ടാഡ ഖ്വവത്ധ.
Copper, Copper, lookit here.
ഠല്ലാല, ഠഠ്ലാല, 'ബും1ട്ബി.
Now, when that fox comes traipsin' along,
8॥ിം സ്ധടാറാ ബപ ്ഖ്ണ ലില്റാണ ൪ ടിവി,
suspectin' nothin’...
1ട്യാദ നസുഭഠ്ച॥ ല്ാദ-ല്വാമ...
Tod?
1ഠഠി?
Oh, boy. These old wings ain't what they used to be.
ചിനല ടമൃഖ്വാ ഡബ്‌ ലവി ഠ്ധ്ധിമ!.
Big Mama, you better lose a few pounds.
ദ്ര ഗീ, !ധ്ധാല്ധ 'ഡബാബബാന്ാദഠ്.
There he is, there he is.
വ്വ റിമ, ധ ഠിഒ.
Tod!
10!
Oh, hi, Big Mama.
൭൨, അ, ദ 'ഗീമണട.
Oh, it's you, Vixey.
പര്വ്വം, എര്യ.
Hey, what brings you way out here?
റല, ല്ാവത്നാാദ്മ ധ്ധദ്ധ്വിഭ ട്ല്‌?
I'm lookin’ for a fox named Tod.
എവ നല്ലി സ്വടാാല്മനട 100.
- He's new here in the forest. - Oh, new?
- ൧9 0ബ ഠ്ക്ാ ഭ സ്ഥല. - പ്പാ ബ?
Well, what does he look like?
810൩, ാലനന്മ ഡ്സ്‌?
Oh, he's young. About your age.
൭൨, ദ സ്വദ. ടലോദ്യ ഠ്വ.
And handsome.
2 -161ിം1
Handsome? Oh, say.
ദ്രാലിറ ചിലി.
Gee, he sure sounds nice.
77൭൩, ലിഗ കസ.
I'm not doing anything.
൧൮ മഗധ ല്വാമ-ഖ്വാമ.
I'll help you find him.
എവ ടിബാലസ്ധ ത്വ ദി ഠി.
Come on. He's gotta be around here somewhere.
1-111-11 ൧19 1ല്ധ ഠി ഠി ട്വ.
Wha...?
൧൧൭...
What happened? Where am I?
൧൧൭ ലി? ചവ ഠി നന്മ?
So, it's you again?
പഠി, മ്ധ ൭?
You barged in on me last night, and now you...
[ഗിണ ഠി ത്വ ഠാ 1ലുടട-റുട, ഠ്്ബിന്ന്‌ ത്വ...
I didn't mean to.
൧൮ മാട്‌ ഥലൃബ.
Just look at the mess you made.
1൦9 ൩ ഠ്ടലാദ്നത്ധവാധദ.
Dagnabit, you clumsy bonehead!
ചിനല്പത്ധ ടി രാം രട്്‌
I'm sorry. It was an accident.
ഗാലീിത്ഥ വ. ബല: ടന്യദ്യ.
Excuses, excuses.
ചടട, ടട.
Mr. Digger, sir? It was so too an accident.
50. ഥല്‌, ബണ്‌? ധമബഒ ടദ്ധഡ ണമ.
You keep out of this, you walkin’ pincushion.
ദ്ധ ഖ്വോാധ മന, ധ്ധലാസ്നമ സബാ ധാജുല്ല
You shouldn't be so grumpy to someone who's new in the neighborhood.
ദ്ധ നല്‌ ടബ്‌ ബു ടാ ബിടി.
A stranger?
ലു ടന?
Why don't you go back where you came from?
(രന്ല്വാ ദ്ധ ലിഗാധിണയ ര ന്യാ മടി ധ്വ?
Wha...?
൧൧൭...
Well, go on.
൭, യ.
Get goin’. Git!
ദലുല്ഖ്ല്ഡഖ്ല്‍്‌
Gosh, he seems so... ! don't know, so downhearted, Big Mama.
൧൧൮൨. ഠി നന്വാസയ... ചവ 1൭ 1ടഡ, നാണ ഠോ, 8 'ഗീടന3.
Well, you can't blame him, honey.
ദ്ധ മിഗാില ടലിദ്വ്ക്ഥ ഠി, ടത.
He was dropped out here and left all alone without a friend in the world.
൧19 ഠി0ാദിത്ഥ ഠ।ട്ബി ടമ ഠി ഠ। ദ്ധ.
Well, maybe there's something I could do.
മംത! മ ടടട്ധബ്ബ ൮ ല്വവാംല്വാധദ്‌.
You know, cheer him up.
ദ്ധ ലി്ധില, ഘാന ഠി.
Honey, you just said the magic words.
ദയറാ, യ്ധാബ ട്വ ടലാഥ്്വാലിയ്മ്ന ലയി.
Now...
ടലിയ്വനാ...
What? But Big Mama, I don't...
൧൭൦ ല്ല ദു 'ഗീമന, മവ ലി.
Darlin’, don't move. You look beautiful.
ദയറാ, ബായി ദ്ധ നന്വാ പി
Thank you.
ലന മടി.
Mornin’, Tod.
ലന 0ഠ॥, 700.
Hello, Big Mama.
ലിലം, 81 [ഗീടന3.
Last night was pretty miserable for you, wasn't it, honey?
[ഗിണ ഠി ടഥാാധ്‌ നസിയ ്ധിലത്ഖ, ൦, ടത?
Just terrible.
ട॥ഭ്വാദ്ധി.
Cheer up and look around.
ലംഗ്ലിത്ഥ ന ॥നമഭ്വനസ്വ.
The forest is beautiful this morning.
ധനി ദേസിഥാാ! ബ്‌.
After last night, nothin' looks beautiful.
ഭലിലാമട (ഭ്യഠിന ന്ലിടണ ടി, 151: ടാഡാധന നന്പാ പി
Wow!
ഗിവ്‌
Who...? Who is that?
ടപ്യാമ...? ടില്വാദവ്ധ?
Oh, just another fox.
൭൨, ബ്ന ടടല്യ സ്പടബണ 1൭ഠ!.
A lady fox.
ഗ്രടഘാലാലിന്മ.
Golly!
ഗിവ്‌
Is she beautiful!
ചാതി സിസ ഠി!
l wonder what her name is.
ടില്വാ റിസ നനബ൭.
Well, why don't you go ask her?
(രന്ല്വാ ത്വ മയി ബര ഠി?
Yeah. Yeah, guess... Guess I will.
൨൭. മ, 9൦... മിവ ൭.
I'll... I'll. go up to her and I'll say, "You're the most gorgeous...
൧൮ 1൭൨... ലയി ാദഠബുദ ഠ്യ, "1ര്ധില്സന ന യ...
The most beautiful...
ണാ ലന സീം...
Never seen anyone, anywhere...” I'll say...
1ലിവാലന്മ്‌ ൫൫ ടടട്ല്വാദ, ഠി നന്ന...” ലവ ടിത്ലിത്ട...
Hi.
൨51.
Hello.
ല്‍.
- Big Mama told me, you know... - [just happened to be...
- 8109 ഴി ലാല്ല്ഡ വ, ത്വ ലസ... - വ ശ്വാ്ധിദ്സ...
May I call you by your first name?
8ഠില ല്വവാാഠ॥ ത്വ ബന നന ലാല്മനട ട്വ?
Oh, sure. Why not?
൭൨, സ്വ. !രന്ജ്വാദന്ഠ്ല്റ്‌
Thanks, but what...? What is your first name?
ലന മടി, ദ്വ ദ്3...? ൧൧൭ നന മണ്ഡ?
- Vixey.
- ഗീത.
My name is... is... Tod.
പ്ൂംനമവ ല്ല... 5151... 709.
Tod?
1ഠഠി?
That's a... That's a nice name, Tod.
വ ടാ... ഖനന സിം ൦.
It looks like that farm boy is makin’ it big with her.
പും സ്ഥലിസാധഠ്ലിറ്ടട ഡ ്ല്വാലുദട ഠ്ണാ്സഒ.
Now just keep it down.
ലന്നു നാലും.
Well, Tod, you know something?
819611, 1700, ദല ഒ?
This stream is just full of trout.
ധാ ൩ ലാഡ്‌ ഠനബ്യേമ്ബിത്ഥ നാഥ്‌.
Do you think you could catch one?
ദ്ധ ഒട ത്ധാഠില്വ്ടാത്വാ ടടട്യ?
- One what? - One what? Fish, silly!
- ലയ ല്വാദ? - ൭%ല്യ ല്വാദ? യി, ഠഠ൦)
Oh, oh, yeah! Oh, yeah.
൭൨, പുല്‍! ൩൮൭.
My dear young lady...
ദദഠിട സ്വധാ ടദൃാ!വ...
.. you happen to be looking at an expert... fisher fox.
.ചിത്ധ ടലാലസ്ാല്ിലാന ബു ടി സ്വടറാ... 0ടഘഖ ഹണ്യഃ॥.
Oh, Tod, Tod. Don't overdo it.
൨൨1൦൦, 190. പടനാ്ബ്നക്ചലില്ധമ്.
I know all the tricks. In fact, I... ! never miss.
൧വദ്ധ ടനസ്പബുദ. ലോലം, ടവ... 9ലാല്മ മാല.
Please let him catch a fish.
1010൦0151൩, ലാലി ഠി 1ടാിത്വാ ടലല്യ യ.
Here comes a whopper!
ബി ഠദ ടടല്രലു്ബാവാടട്‌
Now, watch closely.
ടലയ്വാ, 115 ലിലാദിം
Tod, do you need help?
10, യ്വലാല്ധാദ്ധണ്‌?
No. No, I do it this way
114൦ നിലം മിവ ഥല്‌
all... all the... all the time!
ടലി... ടഖില്ാ... യ!
I got him.
൧൮ ഠില്വാമ ഠി.
Oh, that farm boy, he don't know nothin’ about fishin’.
റ്പാധഠ്ടറഥടട ഡ, ഠി ലിവല്ഡ ഖറാത്വാിക്ന.
He ain't gonna hook her that way.
൧19 15100 ഠ്ല്വാദ ഗ്നു ഠദ ലവ.
Oh, gosh!
൭൨, ലവ!
Tod, you're the funniest thing I ever saw!
10, ധ്ധിടസുണാവഖ ടലര!॥ ൮ ന്ന ല്ഡൃധ്വാ!
Go ahead! Go ahead and laugh!
ബട്ടന്‌ 1ബടിയ്ബിട്നക്വ്മിയ്ധ!
You're like everyone else around here.
(ദ്ധ നദ ൦-൦ ബാ ഠ। ട്ബ്‌.
I'm sorry. I can't help it. You are so funny.
ഗ്‌. ൧൮ 1ടിവാംില്ല്മ്ന. ദ്ധ ടന്യാധ്സ്ധബ.
So I can't fish!
പഠി ടവ ലാല 1ാിത്വാവിയ്ല്‍്‌
You're a silly,
ദ്ധ ടാ ൮൭൩൭ 0൦00൦1,
empty-headed... female!
0ലല്വാധ... ഭ്യാല്മരടംഘാ!
Now just a minute.
പ്ൂംസി ഠ്വ.
I mean, you've got a nerve. Why don't you grow up?
ഗിഭ്ധഠിവ,ത്ധാല്ബ്ബ വര. 8൦ിലന ത്വ ്സ്ഠിവാധഠ്ട്ലാധഠ്ല്റ
Tod, that's no way to talk to Vixey.
10, ഡവാധിത്ന ലേ ലയ്വാ ബു ഗര.
Oh, raspberries! I've had it.
ദ്വ ൧൮ മില ലന 11.
Honey, don't stay mad.
ദയറാ, ന്ന്ട്ട്‌ ടല.
You gotta be natural. That's the trick.
ദ്ധ നട്ടി ട്ടാ. ധില ഖ്യസ.
Can't you see?
ദ്ധ ലിഗനന്വാലിഠിത്ന?
When you have a natural attraction
219 4൭൧ റ്ദ്ലാ൭॥ ഒക ടലനഥ്്യടധ്‌
You deserve a mutual reaction
കഥ നട്ട ടട ഥഖബ്ഥലടടണെ
You're gonna get a whole lot
(രഥ ഒറ ദ്ദ ലാലഥാറട
Of satisfaction
4(്വാഥടെ്ഗ
Here's all you gotta do
൨ഒ0 (൭൧ ൧ഖ൧ ൧൧൭
When you feel that
219 4൭൧ നല്ടടഒ
Natural affection
(ഒക ടലനഥ്ല്യടധ്‌
Leads you in the positive direction
ഗ്ഖ്വാഗട (൭൧൪ ൭൭൧ )൭൧0 ൧൭.50
You gotta stop showin’ off
രഥ ലന്‌ നലഥ്വ്ഥ്‌:
Start showin' up
70൧9 നഹെ്ഥാഥ്ത്ഥ
With little old natural you
൧൧൭ ലോഗ്‌ രഥുര്ഥറ്റ (ഖന
Yes, you gotta appreciate the lady
ക, (ഒഥ നട്ട ഗട്! ടന്‌ ഗല
And now that is a natural fact
ഥു 4 ദ്ദ ഒട
‘Cause when you be yourself
ഴ്ലാദ൧ ൭൧ ലാല്‌ ഗ്ന രഥ
With the lady, yeah
൧ാറ്റ റ്‌ ഗ്ഥൃഭ
You gonna get appreciated
കഥ ഒര്ഥ വ്റ0൭്ഹ൭
Right back
ഴ്ലാദറ്റട! ൧ഒ(ഒ ഒറു
- But Big Mama... - It's just getting interesting.
- ല്ല ദു 'ഗീ5ന3... - ൩ റല സ്ധില്യടഠി നട്മ്ലിം
Tod, I...
100, ലിവ...
I just know you're gonna love the forest.
എവ ല്ധിത്ധ ലിത്വ ട്ധിയ ഡബ്‌.
Listen, come on. Let me show you around.
ഉലാല, നില. ഗി ലിവ ഡബ്ഥിസയ വാദി ദ്വ.
Sure.
ല്വ ടല.
Come on.
1-111-11
Look. One, two, three, four, five, six.
1൦ ടബ്വ, ദ്ധ, 1939, ല്വാട്‌, നട, ലന.
Seven.
ന്ധി.
I think six would be just right.
എവ മട ല്മന ഠി ലിവ.
Six?
ന്‌?
Six what?
50ണ ല്ലാ?
"No hunting."
"॥ല് നാഥ."
Well, now, we ain't gonna do none of that, are we, Copper?
81961, റ്9 ടധ്ധദ്വ്ല, ധി ലവ, ഠഠ്ലാാല്‌?
We're just gonna get us a no-good fox.
൯൩൭ നല്ഡ ഠ്ല്ാബ്ത്ന ടയ സ്വട 13ഗൃഥ്ന൭.
All right, boy, get trackin’.
8109൩, ഗയ] നില!
Smell him out.
ദ്ധ.
What ya got there, Copper?
൧൧൭ ന്ധ ഠ്ല്വാദഡ, ഠ്ല്ാല്‌?
Good work, boy.
ാറ്ധട ത്വ, നി
He'll be comin’ right through here, headin’ for water.
൧19 പിഖ്ഥ ട്ടാ ॥ിധ്‌ട്ല, നലസ്ധ്ധ ൭ 0.
But he won't be drinkin’ any.
ല്ല ഠി 151 ത്ന ഠ്ല്വാദന്്ധബണ.
What a beautiful morning, Vixey.
ചാത്ര.
You know, I've never been happier.
ദ്ധ ല്ഡ, മിവ ൭ 0൦൩൭11 ടലാല്നമ്യാദ ബ.
Oh, Tod, me too.
൭൨, 10, മിഡ്വാഥ ലാസ.
That does it.
ധിലി ഠി.
Amos, you crafty old coot.
൧നനഠട, വ ടി ഡു
The devil himself couldn't have done no better.
॥॥5 വാന 191൦1൨ ധട്ിലാ ഠ്‌.
Tod?
1ഠഠി?
- Tod, wait a minute. - What is it, Vixey?
- 10, ്ഥാഠ്൨ ട്വ. - യാ ഠി, അത്യ?
I don't wanna go in there. It's too quiet.
ചവ ലിഗ്മ്ധ ലായ! ഭ ട്ട. 9 ലില്ധ ടി.
Vixey.
ഗാര്യ.
Tod, be careful.
100, ലാലി.
Dad blast it! He's gettin’ away!
ഠബഭ്യാമ്്‌ ൧ ഠ്ല്ാദ്ധിലി!
Quick, Vixey!
പോഷ്‌, ഗരത്യ്‌
Go on, head for the burrow.
ലലറ്റി, ധര ധാാ ന്മ.
Quick, Vixey. Out the back.
ലോ, ഗര. ॥ഡ്വാലലിയ്ന.
Tod!
10!
Oh, no, Tod.
ധപ്യണാ൦. 7൦൭.
Copper! Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല! ഠഠലാഥാല!
We got 'em now for sure. This is their only way out.
[ഗ്മ ാ35॥ ഠ്‌ ഠ്ച്ാമ ഒ. ബില ട്വ ഭ്ധല നലല്‍൭.
Steady, boy. Steady. Get ready.
ദല. 8 നലല. 86്ട൦ഠിദ.
Tod!
10!
We're trapped!
!ഗ് ബാലയ്റാിയ്വാ!
Tod, I'm scared.
10, ലിവ ടിയ.
Quick, Vixey! This is our only chance!
പോഷ്‌, ഗരത്യ്‌ ബില ട്വ ഹാല്ധബാ ൯൭!
Whoa! No! I don't believe it!
പുംസ! ന്റ ചവ മവാണമല്‍!
Copper, we've trapped him now!
ഠല്ലാല, ൯൭ ഠ്ല്വാലബായ്വാ ഠി!
Copper!
ഠല്ല്ാല്‌!
Tod!
10!
Tod?
1ഠഠി?
Come on, Copper. Get outta the way.
ഗി, ലാല. പനാ നംഘന്ല്ണ.
Well...
൭...
..come on, boy.
ഒവി, നലം
Let's go home.
[ഗി ധി.
This is it.
ബില ഠി.
We got him for sure now.
[ഗ്മ ാ350 ഠ്ല്വാദ ഠി ടല.
Oh, my gosh!
൨, ടിണല്ഠ
What happened?
൧൧൭ ലി?
Hey, there's somethin'
0൭൦, മഠ9 ടടട്ധദ്ധ
very familiar about those eyes, Dinky.
11111111: 1111-11
Nah, it couldn't be.
1ടിപ്ല്റിയ്വില.
Could it?
ഗ്ധഘിന്സ്ത്ന?
Bye, Squeeks. Bye.
ലന്‌ ന്ന്യാി, ടറ്ധടല്‍൭. ലമ ന്ന്യാല.
Good luck, honey.
ലാറു ടലടന, ടയ.
Ouch! You're killin' me! Ouch!
എലി ധ്വനി മയ്‌ ൧ാ്ധിവ്‌
Amos Slade, will you hold still?
൧നഠട ട3ഠില, ാ0ില്വിന്ധ ഠിണ?
You're behaving like a child.
!ദ്ധാണലബാലി നന 0ധഠ്ദ്ലാധഠ്മ
Well, for gosh sakes, you're hurtin' my foot, woman!
൭, ടലാല്ലസ്യ, വ ടിസി ലിവ, ലാലഭന്വാധബ്‌
Nonsense! Your foot is mendin' fine.
ദ്യ വ ദ്വ ടണ്ബാധ്‌ ്ണബബാദിം
You'll soon be yourself.
ല്ലി ഠി ധ്ധ ടസ്ബാധ് നട 01953.
Oh, land sakes. I don't know if I like that.
൭൨, 1൦151. എവ ല്വല്ഡതിദ്ധ ട്വ ടിയ.
Be careful! Ouch!
ലിന്റ! ലിവ
He's sure makin’ a big fuss over a little old hurt leg.
൧19 ൩ നല്പാടടല്പാടടല്ിത്ന വനത 5൭൩ ട൦൦॥൨ബ.
Copper?
€ഠഥഥല?
You're my very best friend.
കഥ (നെ ദ്വ.
And you're mine too, Tod.
ഥു (൭൧൧൧ ൧൧. 70൨.
And we'll always be friends forever, won't we?
ഥു (ഗ്ഒ ഒര്ഥ൭൨്‌ രഥ ട്ലഒ7ട9-(ഒനഒഥ)൭, ൧ഥ്‌ര്ഥ സ്ര
Yeah, forever.
൭, ടലഒ൭ന9-9ന൭൨൮)൭.